Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Western Filmscripts Acquired Before July 1996, 1918-1989
  - Tequila Sunrise, January 14, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 354)
    Actors: [Mel Gibson Michelle Pfeiffer Kurt Russell]
    Production company: Cinema City Films
    Setting: Contemporary Southern California
  - Texans Never Cry, June 14, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 355)
    Actors: Gene Autry Pat Buttram Gail Davis
  - The Texas Kid, July 25, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 356)
    Story: [Lynton Brent]
    Screenplay: [Jess Bowers (Adele Buffington)]
    Actors: [Johnny Mack Brown Raymond Hatton Shirley Patterson]
    Notes: Working title: High School
  - The Texas Rangers, April 9, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 357)
    Story: [King Vidor]
    Screenplay: [Louis Stevens]
    Actors: [Fred MacMurray Jack Oakie Jean Parker]
  - A Texas Scandal (Box 49, Folder 358)
    Screenplay: Arthur Ripley
    Production company: Normandy Productions
    Notes: "Submitted to Ronald Reagan" label on cover. Mitchell Gertz agency.
  - There Was A Crooked Man..., September 3, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 359)
    Director: Joseph Mankiewicz
    Producer: Joseph Mankiewicz
    Actors: Kirk Douglas Henry Fonda Warren Oates
    Production company: Kinney National Company
    Distributor: Warner Brothers-Seven Arts
    Setting: State Penitentiary
    Notes: Script is prepared for translation.
  - These Thousand Hills, May 22, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 360)
    Screenplay: Alfred Hayes
    Director: [Richard Fleischer]
    Actors: Don Murray Lee Remick [Richard Egan]
    Setting: 1880, Oregon
  - Those Redheads from Seattle, March 12, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 361)
    Screenplay: Lewis R. Foster [Geoffrey Homes George Worthing Yates]
    Director: [Lewis R. Foster]
    Producer: [William H. Pine William C. Thomas]
    Actors: [Rhonda Fleming Agnes Moorehead Gene Barry]
    Type: Revised final white
    Notes: "Troy Sanders" written on cover. Working title: Those Sisters from Seattle.
  - Those Redheads from Seattle, January 27, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 362)
    Notes: "Troy Sanders" written on cover. Working title: Sisters from Seattle.
  - Three Mesquiteers, June 13,1940 (Box 50, Folder 363)
    Setting: Post Spanish American war
    Notes: A late entry of the Three Mesquiteers series. Specific title not available.
  - The Three Mesquiteers, 1936 release (Box 50, Folder 364)
    Story: William Colt MacDonald
    Producer: Nat Levine
    Actors: Robert Livingston Ray Corrigan Syd Saylor
    Notes: "Milt" written on cover.
  - Three were Thoroughbreds, November 18, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 365)
    Notes: "Bob Young," "Meet the Missus" written on the cover. Annotated.
  - Three Young Texans, July 14, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 366)
    Story: [William MacLeod Raine]
    Screenplay: Gerald Drayson Adams
    Director: [Henry Levin]
    Actors: Mitzi Gaynor Jeffrey Hunter [Keefe Brasselle]
    Setting: Maverick County, Texas
  - A Ticket to Tomahawk, June 24, 1949; November 9, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 367)
    Screenplay: Mary Loos Richard Sale
    Director: Richard Sale
    Producer: Robert Bassler
    Actors: Dan Dailey Anne Baxter Rory Calhoun
    Type: Revised final; revised added scenes and retakes
    Notes: "Harry Carter" written on cover
  - Timber Wolf, [1925 release] (Box 50, Folder 368)
    Screenplay: Jackson Gregory John Stone
    Director: [W. S. Van Dyke]
    Producer: W. S. Van Dyke
    Actors: Buck Jones [Elinor Fair Sam Allen]
    Production company: William Fox Vaudeville Company
    Distributor: William Fox Vaudeville Company
    Setting: Southwestern Timber
    Notes: Silent film. No "327" stamped on wrapper. Divided by shots and scenes.
  - A Time for Dying (Box 50, Folder 369)
    Screenplay: Budd Boetticher
    Director: Budd Boetticher
    Producer: Audie Murphy
    Actors: Richard Lapp Budd Randall Bob Random
    Production company: Corinth Films
    Notes: Filmed in 1969, released in 1982.
  - The Time Has Come (Box 51, Folder 370)
    Story: Edgar G. Ulmer
    Screenplay: Bart Lytton
  - The Tin Star, September 19, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 371)
    Story: [Barney Slater Joel Kane]
    Producer: [William Perlberg George Seaton]
    Actors: [Henry Fonda Anthony Perkins Betsy Palmer]
    Setting: Western town, 1888
  - Tom Mix, July 10, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 372)
    Screenplay: Larry Cohen
    Notes: Not released with this title
  - Tonto Basin Outlaws (Subtitle: Tenth in the Range Buster Series), [1941 release] (Box 51, Folder 373)
    Story: Earle Snell
    Screenplay: John Vlahos
    Director: [S. Roy Luby]
    Producer: [George W. Weeks]
    Actors: [Ray Corrigan John King Max Terhune]
    Production company: Range Busters Inc.
    Setting: Colorado, 1898
    Notes: Range Buster Series
  - The Topeka Terror, [1945 release] (Box 51, Folder 374)
    Screenplay: Norman S. Hall [Patricia Harper]
    Producer: [Stephen Auer (assoc)]
    Actors: [Allan "Rocky" Lane Linda Stirling Roy Barcroft]
    Setting: Red Dust, Oklahoma, 1889
  - The Trail of the Lonesome Pine, October 9, 1935 (Box 51, Folder 375)
    Production company: Walter Wanger Productions, Inc.
    Type: Final draft continuity
  - Trail of the Yukon, [1949 release] (Box 51, Folder 376)
    Story: [James Oliver Curwood]
    Director: [William X. Crowley]
    Producer: [Lindsley Parsons]
    Actors: [Kirby Grant Suzanne Dalbert Anthony Warde]
    Distributor: Monogram Studios
    Setting: Canadian Yukon
    Notes: Many passages crossed out or bracketed.
  - Trailin', July 6, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 377)
    Screenplay: Lynn Reynolds
    Producer: Lynn Reynolds
    Actors: Tom Mix [Eva Novak Burt Sprotte]
  - Trails to Two Moons, October 5, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 378)
    Story: Robert Welles Ritchie
    Screenplay: Edward Le Saint
    Producer: Edward Le Saint
    Actors: Buck Jones
    Setting: Teapot Creek, cattle country
  - Trails West (Box 52, Folder 379)
    Production company: Producers Pictures Corp
    Notes: Bobby Clark series.
  - Traveling Saleswoman (Subtitle: Traveling Saleslady), June 25, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 380)
    Screenplay: Howard Dinsdale
    Director: [Charles F. Riesner]
    Actors: [Joan Davis Andy Devine Adele Jergens]
  - The Trial of Billy Jack, [1974 release] (Box 52, Folder 381)
    Screenplay: [Frank Christina Teresa Christina]
    Director: [Frank Laughlin]
    Producer: [Joe Cramer]
    Actors: Delores Taylor Tom Laughlin [Victor Izay]
    Production company: [Taylor-Laughlin]
    Notes: Newspaper clipping of ad for movie taped on cover. "Michael Economou" written on cover.
  - Trigger Trail, April 25, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 382)
    Screenplay: Ed Earl Repp Patricia Harper
    Actors: Rod Cameron Fuzzy Knight Vivian Austin
    Notes: "Willis Cook" written on cover. Newspaper clipping of Vivian Austin enclosed.
  - Triple Threat (Box 52, Folder 383)
    Notes: Range Busters series
  - Two Flags West (Subtitle: Trumpet to the Morn), March 24, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 384)
    Story: Frank S. Nugent Curtis Kenyon
    Screenplay: Casey Robinson [Frank S. Nugent]
    Producer: [Casey Robinson]
    Actors: [Joseph Cotten Linda Darnell Jeff Chandler]
  - The Undefeated, September 18, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 385)
    Story: Stanley Hough
    Actors: [John Wayne Rock Hudson Marian McCargo]
    Setting: Mexico; Tennessee, 1865
  - The Unforgiven, April 1, 1960 April 4, 1960 (Box 52, Folder 386)
    Story: Alan LeMay
    Screenplay: Ben Maddow
    Director: John Huston
    Producer: James Hill
    Actors: Burt Lancaster Audrey Hepburn Audie Murphy
    Production company: James Productions
    Type: Cutting and dialogue continuity
  - The Unsinkable Molly Brown, November 20, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 387)
    Story: [Richard Morris]
    Screenplay: Helen Deutsch
    Director: Charles Walters
    Producer: Lawrence Weingarten
    Actors: Debbie Reynolds Harve Presnell Ed Begley
    Type: Shooting schedule and script
  - Untamed Frontier, May 8, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 388)
    Story: Houston Branch Eugenia Night
    Screenplay: Gerald Drayson Adams John Bagni Gwen Bagni Polly James
    Director: Hugo Fregonese
    Producer: Leonard Goldstein
    Actors: Joseph Cotten Shelley Winters Scott Brady
    Production company: Universal-International Studios
    Distributor: Universal-International Studios
  - Untitled Serial (Subtitle: Episodes 1 - 12), February 18, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 389)
    Director: Pete Adreon
    Type: Estimating shooting script
    Notes: 12 episode serial. Character "Reed"'s lines are underlined
  - Urban Cowboy, February 15, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 390)
    Story: [Aaron Latham]
    Screenplay: Aaron Latham James Bridges
    Director: [James Bridges]
    Producer: [Robert Evans Irving Azoff]
    Actors: [John Travolta Debra Winger Scott Glenn]
    Setting: Texas, 1980's
  - Valdez is Coming, May 20, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 391)
    Screenplay: Roland Kibbee [David Rayfiel]
    Director: [Edwin Sherin]
    Producer: [Roland Kibbee Ira Steiner]
    Actors: [Burt Lancaster Susan Clark Jon Cypher]
    Production company: Norlan Productions
    Setting: US/Mexican Border, 1895
  - The Valientes (Box 53, Folder 392)
    Screenplay: Douglas Heyes
    Setting: Mexico, 1863
    Notes: Handwritten note to "Bud" from Doug Heyes enclosed.
  - Valley of Fire, September 12, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 393)
    Story: [Gerald Geraghty]
    Screenplay: Norman S. Hall [Earle Snell]
    Producer: [Armand Schaefer]
    Actors: [Gene Autry Pat Buttram Gail Davis]
    Setting: Quartz Creek, 1850s
  - Valley Range (Box 54, Folder 394)
    Actors: Gene Autry
    Notes: "Betty Burbridge" written on first page
  - The Vanishing Westerner, October 29, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 395)
    Director: [Philip Ford]
    Actors: [Monte Hale Paul Hurst Aline Towne]
    Setting: Broken Bow
  - Vigilante Force, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 396)
    Screenplay: George Armitage
    Director: George Armitage
    Producer: Gene Corman
    Actors: Kris Kristofferson Jan-Michael Vincent Victoria Principal
  - The Vigilantes Return, April 1, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 397)
    Screenplay: Roy Chanslor
    Director: [Ray Taylor]
    Producer: [Howard Welsch]
    Actors: [Jon Hall Margaret Lindsay Andy Devine]
    Setting: Rattlesnake
    Notes: Revisions and outline of characters included.
  - The Villain, August 16, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 398)
    Screenplay: Robert G. Kane
    Director: [Mort Engelberry]
    Producer: [Hal Needham]
    Actors: Kirk Douglas Ann-Margret Arnold Schwarzenegger
    Production company: Mort Engelberg Productions
    Notes: enclosed cast list
  - The Virginian, May 14, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 399)
    Story: Owen Wister
    Screenplay: Howard Estabrook Grover Jones Keen Thompson Edward E. Paramore, Jr.
    Director: [Victor Fleming]
    Producer: Louis Lighton
    Actors: Gary Cooper Richard Arlen Mary Brian
    Notes: Paramount's first sound Western.
  - Wagons West, September 22, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 400)
    Director: Ford Beebe
    Actors: [Rod Cameron Noah Beery, Jr. Peggie Castle]
    Setting: Wagon train, Missouri
    Notes: Shooting schedule included.
  - Wanted Men (Box 55, Folder 401)
    Screenplay: Harry Fraser
    Production company: Alexander-Stern Productions
    Distributor: Producers Releasing Company
    Setting: Texas Panhandle
  - War Dogs (Box 55, Folder 402)
    Notes: Range Busters series. Working title: Dogs of War.
  - The War Horse, October 27, 1926 (Box 55, Folder 403)
    Story: Buck Jones
    Screenplay: Lambert Hillyer
    Actors: Buck Jones [Lois Todd Lloyd Whitlock]
    Setting: Wyoming, 1917
  - Warlock, July 29, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 404)
    Screenplay: Robert Alan Arthur
    Producer: [Edward Dmytryk]
    Actors: [Richard Widmark Henry Fonda Anthony Quinn]
    Setting: Bucksaw Mountains
  - Warlock, May 21, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 405)
    Setting: Bucksaw mountians
  - Warpath, July 28, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 406)
    Story: [Frank Gruber]
    Screenplay: Frank Gruber
    Director: [Byron Haskin]
    Producer: [Nat Holt]
    Actors: [Edmond O'Brien Dean Jagger Forrest Tucker]
    Production company: Nat Holt Pictures
    Setting: 1870s
  - Way Out West, July 5, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 407)
    Story: Byron Morgan Alfred Block
    Screenplay: Joe Farnum
    Director: Fred Niblo
    Actors: William Harnes Leila Hyams Polly Moran
  - The Way West, [May 20, 1966] (Box 56, Folder 408)
    Story: A.B. Guthrie, Jr.
    Screenplay: Ben Maddow [Mitch Lindemann]
    Producer: [Harold Hecht]
    Actors: [Kirk Douglas Robert Mitchum Richard Widmark]
    Setting: Missouri, 1843
    Notes: All parts relating to Amos Turley are marked in purple ink.
  - The Way West, June 29, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 409)
    Production company: Harold Hecht Company
  - West of Texas, May 10, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 410)
    Notes: Texas Ranger series. Reissued as "Shootin' Irons".
  - Western Union, September 10, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 411)
    Story: [Zane Grey]
    Screenplay: [Robert Carson]
    Director: [Fritz Lang]
    Producer: [Harry Joe Brown, (assoc)]
    Actors: [Robert Young Randolph Scott Dean Jagger]
    Setting: Nebraska, 1860
    Notes: Revisions from September 20, 1940 and December 1940.
  - The Westerner, [1939 release] (Box 56, Folder 412)
    Story: [Stuart N. Lake]
    Screenplay: [Jo Swerling Niven Busch]
    Director: [William Wyler]
    Producer: [Samuel Goldwyn]
    Actors: [Gary Cooper Walter Brennan Doris Davenport]
  - Westworld, January 1973 (Box 56, Folder 413)
    Screenplay: Michael Crichton
    Director: [Michael Crichton]
    Actors: [Yul Brynner Richard Benjamin James Brolin]
    Setting: Future
  - Westworld, January 16, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 414)
    Notes: "No Changes" stamped on cover.
  - Whispering Smith, April 9, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 415)
    Story: [Frank H. Spearman]
    Screenplay: Frank Butler Karl Kamb
    Director: [Leslie Fenton]
    Actors: [Alan Ladd Robert Preston Brenda Marshall]
  - The White Buffalo, [1977 release] (Box 57, Folder 416)
    Story: Richard Sale
    Screenplay: Richard Sale
    Producer: [Pancho Kohner]
    Actors: [Charles Bronson Kim Novak Jack Warden]
    Production company: Dino de Laurentis Company
    Setting: Black Hills
    Notes: Story of Wild Bill Hickock and Crazy Horse
  - White Fang, January 27, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 417)
    Screenplay: Hal Long [Sam Duncan]
    Actors: [Michael Whalen Jean Muir Charles Winninger]
    Setting: Alaska, 1900
  - Wichita, May 28, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 418)
    Director: [Jacques Tourneur]
    Actors: [Joel McCrea Vera Miles Lloyd Bridges]
    Setting: Oklahoma/Kansas Border
  - The Wild Bunch, November 15, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 419)
    Story: [Walon Green] Roy N. Sickner
    Screenplay: Walon Green Sam Peckinpah
    Producer: [Phil Feldman]
    Actors: [William Holden Ernest Borgnine Robert Ryan]
    Production company: Warner Brothers - Seven Arts
    Setting: Southern Texas prairie, 1913
    Type: Revised estimating script
    Notes: Filmed in Mexico. "J. Roberts" written on the cover. Enclosed memo regarding publicity for Stu Gilliam.
  - The Wild Bunch, February 12, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 420)
    Story: Roy N. Sickner [Walon Green]
  - The Wild Rovers, October 9, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 421)
    Screenplay: Blake Edwards
    Director: Blake Edwards
    Producer: Blake Edwards Ken Wales
    Actors: William Holden Ryan O'Neal Karl Malden
    Production company: Geoffrey Productions
    Notes: "Andre Pieterre" written on cover.
  - The Wild Rovers, February 26, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 422)
    Type: Early draft
  - Wings of the Hawk, February 2, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 423)
    Story: [Gerald Drayson Adams]
    Screenplay: James E. Moser
    Director: [Budd Boetticher]
    Producer: [Aaron Rosenberg]
    Actors: [Van Heflin Julia Adams Abbe Lane]
    Setting: Mexico, 1911
  - Winners of the West, February 8, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 424a)
    Screenplay: George H. Plympton Basil Dickey Charles R. Condon
    Director: Ford Beebe Ray Taylor
    Actors: Dick Foran Anne Nagel James Craig
    Notes: Serial - 13 episodes, separately paginated. Folder A: 1-4.
  - Winners of the West, February 8, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 424b)
    Notes: Serial - 13 episodes, separately paginated. Folder B: 5-13.
  - Winning of the West, June 3, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 425)
    Director: George Archainbaud
    Actors: Gene Autry Smiley Burnette [Gail Davis]
    Notes: Shooting schedule enclosed
  - Wyoming Mail, November 25, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 426)
    Story: [Robert Hardy Andrews]
    Screenplay: [Harry Essex Leonard Lee]
    Director: [Reginald LeBorg]
    Producer: [Aubrey Schenck]
    Actors: [Stephen McNally Alexis Smith Howard Da Silva]
    Setting: Wyoming, 1869
  - Wyoming Mail, March 10, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 427)
    Screenplay: Leonard Lee [Harry Essex]
    Director: Reginald LeBorg
    Actors: [Stephen McNally Alexis Smith Howard da Silva]
    Notes: Includes shooting call sheet from 11th day of shooting, May 15, 1950.
  - Wyoming Renegades, June 2, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 428)
    Screenplay: David Lang
    Director: [Fred F. Sears]
    Producer: [Wallace MacDonald]
    Actors: [Phil Carey Martha Hyer Gene Evans]
    Notes: Working title: Wyoming Outlaws.
  - Yaqui Drums, 1956 release (Box 59, Folder 429)
    Story: [Paul Peil]
    Screenplay: D.D. Beauchamp [Jo Pagano]
    Director: [Jean Yarbrough]
    Producer: [William F. Brody]
    Actors: [Rod Cameron Mary Castle J. Carroll Naish]
    Production company: William F. Brody Pictures
  - Yellow Sky, May 14, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 430)
    Actors: Gregory Peck Anne Baxter Richard Widmark
    Setting: A small Western Arizona ghost town, summer 1867.
  - Young Guns, January 8, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 431)
    Screenplay: John Fusco
    Director: Christopher Cain
    Producer: Joe Roth
    Actors: Emilio Estevez Kiefer Sutherland Lou Diamond Philips
    Setting: New Mexico, 1878
    Type: Numbered script
    Notes: Call sheet enclosed. "Neil Summer" on cover.
  - Zandy's Bride, February 26, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 432)
    Story: Lillian Bos Ross
    Screenplay: Marc Norman
    Director: [Jan Troell]
    Producer: [Harvey Matofsky]
    Actors: [Gene Hackman Liv Ullman Eileen Heckart]
  - Zorro-The Gay Blade, October 3, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 433)
    Story: [Hal Dresner Greg Alt Don Moriarty Bob Randall]
    Screenplay: Hal Dresner
    Director: [Peter Medak]
    Producer: [George Hamilton C.O. Erickson]
    Actors: [George Hamilton Lauren Hutton Brenda Vaccaro]
    Production company: Melvin Simon Productions
    Setting: California, 1790s
  - Zorro-The Gay Blade, April 24, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 434)
    Producer: [George Hamilton C. O. Erickson]
    Actors: [Lauren Hutton Brenda Vaccaro George Hamilton]
- Western Filmscripts Acquired After July 1996, 1917-2008
  Arranged alphabetically by title, with dates of scripts provided when available. Scripts bearing the working title are identified as such with the release title following in square brackets, when known.
  - Adventures of Dan Coyote, 1946 July 8 (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Davy Crockett, [circa 1952] (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Don Renegade [The Mark of the Renegade], 1950 June 21 (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Don Renegade [The Mark of the Renegade], 1950 Aug 16 (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Don Renegade [The Mark of the Renegade], 1950 Sep 27 (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Don Renegade [The Mark of the Renegade], 1950 Oct 12 (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Frank and Jesse James, 1948 (Box 60)
  - Adventures of Frank and Jesse James, 1948 (Box 60)
    Includes photographs.
  - Adventures of Red Ryder, 1940 (Box 60)
  - Against a Crooked Sky, 1975 June 11 (Box 60)
  - The Alamo, 1960 September 14 (Box 60)
  - Alaskans [North to Alaska], 1959 February 4 (Box 60)
  - Albuquerque, 1947 September 5 (Box 60)
  - Alexander Simon's Impregnable Gold Tender, 1978 October 23 (Box 60)
  - Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore, 1974 Februrary 4 (Box 60)
  - All American Boy, 1970 March 18 (Box 60)
  - All My Friends Are Going to Be Strangers, [circa 1975] (Box 60)
  - All My Friends Are Going to Be Strangers, 1991 March 18 (Box 60)
  - All the Pretty Horses, [circa 1999] (Box 61)
  - All the Pretty Horses, [circa 2000] (Box 61)
  - Along the Mohawk Trail, 1946 June 25 (Box 61)
  - Along the Oregon Trail, 1946 August 7-9 (Box 61)
  - An American Tail II, 1988 September 18 (Box 61)
  - An American Tail II, 1989 July 21 (Box 61)
  - Amigos, 1969 January 15 (Box 61)
  - Any Which Way You Can, 1980 (Box 138)
    Contains second draft, and shooting schedule.
  - Anything to Survive, 1990 February 5 (Box 61)
  - Apache Trail, 1952 March 25 (Box 61)
  - The Apple Dumpling Gang, 1974 June 17 (Box 61)
  - The Apple Dumpling Gang, 1981 November 6 (Box 61)
  - Arctic Manhunt, 1948 August 12 (Box 61)
  - Arctic Manhunt, 1948 November 24 (Box 61)
  - Arctic Manhunt, 1949 March 2 (Box 61)
  - The Arizona Raiders, 1964 November 9 (Box 61)
  - Arizona Redman [Arizona Frontier], 1940 June 18 (Box 61)
  - Arizona Sunset [Range Renegades], [1948] (Box 61)
  - Arizona Trail, 1943 October 1 (Box 61)
  - The Awakening Land (Subtitle: Part One: The Trees), 1977 July 19 (Box 61)
  - The Awakening Land (Subtitle: Part Two: The Fields), 1977 July 25 (Box 61)
  - The Awakening Land (Subtitle: Part Three: The Town) [two copies], 1977 October 14; 2 (Box 61)
  - Bachelor in Paradise, 1961 March 15 (Box 62)
  - Back in the Saddle, [1941] (Box 62)
  - Back to God's Country, [circa 1946] (Box 62)
  - Back to God's Country, 1946 May 13 (Box 62)
  - Back to God's Country, 1952 December 23 (Box 62)
  - Back to God's Country, 1953 January 8 (Box 62)
  - Back to God's Country, 1953 July 20 (Box 62)
  - Backlash, 1955 December 28 (Box 62)
  - Backlash, 1956 January 26 (Box 62)
  - Bad Boy, 1949 (Box 62)
  - Bad Company, 1970 December (Box 62)
  - Bad Girls, 1992 August 21 (Box 62)
  - Bad Girls, 1993 June 22 (Box 62)
  - Bad Girls, 1993 August 17-30 (Box 62)
  - Bad Lands of Dakota [Badlands of Dakota], [circa 1940] (Box 62)
  - Bad Lands of Dakota [Badlands of Dakota], 1941 June 3 (Box 62)
  - Bad Man from Red Butte, 1940 May 4 (Box 62)
  - Badge of Evil, 1957 January 21 (Box 62)
  - Badlands [Soldiers Three], 1961 May 10 (Box 62)
  - Badlands, 1972 June (Box 62)
  - Badlands of Dakota, 1941 August 21 (Box 62)
  - Badman's Territory, 1945 July 26 (Box 62)
  - Baja Oklahoma, 1983 April 8 (Box 63)
  - Ballad of Cable Hogue, 1968 July 26 (Box 63)
  - Ballad of Cable Hogue, [1970] (Box 63)
  - Ballad of Little Jo, 1991 February 18 (Box 63)
  - The Bandit [The Ride to Hangman's Tree], 1966 May 10 (Box 63)
  - Bandolero!, 1967 September 18 (Box 63)
  - The Bank Robber, [circa 1969] (Box 63)
  - The Bank Robber, 1970 August 28 (Box 63)
  - Barbarosa, 1981 December 15 (Box 63)
  - The Barbary Coast, 1975 February 28 (Box 63)
  - Baron of Arizona, 1950 February 1 (Box 63)
  - Barricade, 1949 April 4 (Box 63)
  - Barrier, 1937 November 3 (Box 63)
  - Battle at Apache Pass, 1951 October 8 (Box 63)
  - Battling with Buffalo Bill, 1941 (Box 63)
  - The Beautiful Blonde from Bashful Bend, 1948 September 23 (Box 64)
  - Bells of Capistrano, [1942] (Box 64)
  - Bells of Capistrano, [1942] (Box 64)
  - Bells of Coronado, 1949 July 20 (Box 64)
  - Bend of the River, 1951 December 5 (Box 64)
  - Beneath Western Skies [Pride of the West], 1938 March 29 (Box 64)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1980 April 24 (Box 64)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1981 April 14 (Box 64)
  - Beyond the Last Frontier, 1943 June 19; 2 (Box 64)
  - The Big Country, 1958 (Box 138)
  - A Big Hand for the Little Lady, 1965 July 9 (Box 64)
  - Big Harpe [Big Jack], 1948 August 18 (Box 64)
  - Big House, U.S.A., 1954 September 1 (Box 64)
  - Big River, Big Man, 1960 August 8 (Box 64)
  - The Big Show, [1936] (Box 64)
  - The Big Test, 1955 July 27 (Box 64)
  - Big Wednesday [two copies], [circa 1977]; 2 (Box 64)
  - Billy the Kid, 1940 September 28 (Box 64)
  - Black Bart [two copies], 1947 May 20; 2 (Box 65)
  - Black Bart, 1948 January 22 (Box 65)